{
    "subject": "resource/Porsche_911_GT1",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Porsche 911 GT1 Stra\u00dfenversion",
    "human_readable": "The name of Porsche 911 GT1 is Porsche 911 GT1 Stra\u00dfenversion.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9886221289634705,
            "question": "What is the name of the Porsche 911 GT1 Stra\u00dfenversion?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9734470844268799,
            "question": "What are some notable features of the Porsche 911 GT1 Stra\u00dfenversion?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.970939576625824,
            "question": "When was the Porsche 911 GT1 Stra\u00dfenversion released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9665447473526001,
            "question": "Are there any special editions of the Porsche 911 GT1 Stra\u00dfenversion?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9424078464508057,
            "question": "Is there a difference between the Porsche 911 GT1 and the Porsche 911 GT1 Stra\u00dfenversion?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.896935760974884,
            "question": "What type of vehicle is the Porsche 911 GT1?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.887888491153717,
            "question": "What is the legacy of the Porsche 911 GT1 Stra\u00dfenversion in automotive history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8565267324447632,
            "question": "What is the target market for the Porsche 911 GT1 Stra\u00dfenversion?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7921500205993652,
            "question": "How does the Porsche 911 GT1 Stra\u00dfenversion perform compared to other models in its class?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.464718222618103,
            "question": "What does 'Stra\u00dfenversion' mean in German?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Porsche 911 GT1 is Porsche 911 GT1 Stra\u00dfenversion.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5255_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does the Porsche 911 GT1 Stra\u00dfenversion perform compared to other models in its class?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5255_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the target market for the Porsche 911 GT1 Stra\u00dfenversion?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5255_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the legacy of the Porsche 911 GT1 Stra\u00dfenversion in automotive history?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5255_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5255_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5255_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5255_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5255_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5255_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5255_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5255_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5255_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5255_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5255_76.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that all five documents mention the term \"Porsche 911 GT1\" and/or \"Porsche 911 GT1 Stra\u00dfenversion\", which suggests that they are referring to the same vehicle."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention the 911 GT1 Strassenversion, which is essentially another name for the Porsche 911 GT1. Therefore, the statement that the name of the Porsche 911 GT1 is Porsche 911 GT1 Stra\u00dfenversion is supported by the context information provided."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}